Guide to the Lucien L. Nunn papers [ca.1863-1971]
Nunn, Lucien L. papers [ca.1863-1971]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lucien L. Nunn papers, [ca. 1863-1971]
37-4-1770
Lucien L. Nunn, 1853-1925.
ca. 53 cubic ft.
Correspondence; photographs and negatives; maps, blueprints, and specifications; clippings; addresses and lectures; printed material; reports; constitution, by-laws, and amendments; financial records; applications; minutes; and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers documenting the career of Lucien L. Nunn.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Electrical engineer. Lucien L. Nunn founded the Telluride Power Company in Telluride, Colorado, and the Telluride Association, a student-managed organization which provides housing and other assistance for intellectually gifted high school and college students at Cornell University and at Deep Springs, California.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence; photographs and negatives; maps, blueprints, and specifications; clippings; addresses and lectures; printed material; reports; constitution, by-laws, and amendments; financial records; applications; minutes; and other papers documenting the career of Lucien L. Nunn, his founding and direction of the Telluride Association, and the development of the electrical power industry in the United States, including information concerning the Telluride Motor Company, Telluride Power Company, and Ontario Power Company. Also, manuscript history of Telluride by Orville Sweeting. Black and white photographs of Telluride Association Conventions, 1911-1960 and CD with pdf copies of photographs. DVD titled "Hydro Power" from the Rocky Mountain PBS series Colorado Experience, season 2 (2014).
Letters from L.L. Nunn to Wallace Cook.
Family letters, primarily to L. L. Nunn,1863-1938, 1881-1882 (bulk) include original letters, many with typescript transcripts, as well as photocopies. Correspondents include his mother, Miriam Kendall Nunn, his brothers Josiah J. Nunn and Frederick Thomas Nunn, and especially his sister Nellie. 1846 Bible given to L. L. Nunn by his grandmother, Mary Towler Kendall and an 1867 Concordance owned by Nunn. Also, Nunn family genealogy sheets, copies of "snippets" from the diaries of Alice Bird (L. L. Nunn's niece), and three photographs.
Group photographs of members of the Cornell Branch of the Telluride Association, 1910-1960.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Nunn, L. L. (Lucien Lucius), 1853-1925.; Sweeting, Orville J., 1913-; Whitman, Carroll.; Cornell University--Graduate students.; Cornell University--Students.; Ontario Power Company.; Utah Power and Light Company.; Deep Springs College.; Telluride Association.; Telluride Motor Company.; Telluride Power Company.
Subjects:
Electric utilities.; Education--Societies, etc.
Form and Genre Terms:
Blueprints.; Maps.; Specifications.; Negatives.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Some Telluride Association newsletters and photographs from this collection are available online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/29989
An extensive amount of additional digitized material, compiled by Denis Clark, regarding Nunn, Telluride Power, Deep Springs and the Telluride Association is available on DVD #809 within this collection. Some of the material is from Cornell, but the DVD also contains files from other sources.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collections: Deep Springs College Records, #6428; Oral History Interviews for Deep Springs College and Telluride Association, #37-4-4042; and John Burchard papers, #6793, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMM06793. See also the book The Electric Edge of Academe.
SERIES LIST
Series I. L.L. Nunn-Personal
Boxes: 1-3, 29, 30, 61, 68
Biographical Information
Correspondence and Documents
Financial and Legal Records
Publications Belonging to Nunn
Photographs
Miscellany and Nunn's Personal Effects
Series II. Carroll Whitman
Box: 3
Correspondence
Financial Records
Miscellany
Series III. Telluride Power Company and the Power Industry
Boxes: 4-10, 31, 32
Correspondence and Related Documents
Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes
Legal Documents
Papers, Addresses, & Reports
News Clippings, Articles & Other Publications
Maps, Drawings, Blueprints, Graphs, Charts etc.
Photographs, Illustrations, & Negatives
Miscellany
Beaver River Power Company
Big Springs Power Company
Ontario Power Company
The Power Company, Norris Montana
Wyoming Electric
Its Predecessor - San Miguel Consolidated Gold Mining Company
Its Successor - Utah Power & Light Company
Telluride Institute
Other Power Industry Companies
Power Industry Publications
Power Industry Miscellany
Series IV. Telluride Association
Boxes: 12-18, 20-21, 63-67, 5 loose volumes
Alumni
Committees
Conventions
Corporation
Correspondence and Documents
Custodians
Financial and Legal Records
Lectureships
Reports
Miscellany
Branches
Publications
Series V. Deep Springs
Boxes: 18-19
Correspondence and Documents
Financial Records
Student Body Minutes
Miscellany
Photographs
Publications
Series VI. Photographs
Boxes: 26-28, 43, 62,71
Places: Survey Photography, Landscapes, Interiors, etc.
Electrical, Mining, and Mill Interests
Deep Springs
Telluride Association and House
Miscellaneous and Unidentified
Photograph Negatives
People: Portraiture, Individual, and Group Photographs
Electrical, Mining, and Mill Interests
Deep Springs
Telluride Association and House
Miscellaneous and Unidentified
Technical
Nunn Personal
Series VII. Miscellany
Boxes: 10-11, 64, 65, 71, 1 loose volume
Series VIII. Orville Sweeting
Boxes: 22-25
General
Correspondence
Research Material
Sweeting Photo Project
Manuscript
CONTAINER LIST
- Digital material, 809
  A number of items from this collection have been digitized and are available online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/29989
  Additionally, an extensive amount of digitized material, compiled by Denis Clark, regarding Nunn, Telluride Power, Deep Springs and the Telluride Association is available on DVD #809 within this collection. Some of the material is from Cornell, but the DVD also contains files from other sources.
- Series I. L.L. Nunn - Personal
  - Biographical Information
    - Hardcover-L.L. Nunn: A Memoir, by Stephen A. Bailey, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Paperback-L.L. Nunn: A Memoir, by Stephen A. Bailey (with hand written chronology in back), 1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence & Documents
    - Bown, J. Clinton (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Savings & Trust Company, Cleveland, Ohio (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Diehl, Harry E., May 6, 1905 - December 2, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Fairbanks, R.P. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - First National Bank of Telluride (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Kean Taylor & Company (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - King Motor Car Company & Chambers Motor Company, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Lasell Seminary, Auburndale, Mass., 1895-1901 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1901-1904 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1913-1916 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Monarch Tractor Company (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Nunn, P.N., 1905-1907 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Parrott Tractor Company (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Parrott Tractor Company (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Rogers, Nathan (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Salt Lake & Mercur Railroads (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Smoot, H.E. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Smoot, H.E. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Utah Lake Irrigation Company, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Walcott, Charles D. I (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Walcott, Charles D. II (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Wegg, Donald R. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Woodland, H. (Allis Chalmers Manufacturing Company) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - re: Woods Hole Marine Biological Laboratory (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Nunn family and H. E. Smoot correspondence. (Box 29)
      Formerly in box 48.
  - Financial & Legal Records
    - Finacial Records, 1905-1909 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cash Balances I, 1920-1925 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Cash Balances II, 1920-1925 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Check Books, 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Check Books, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Check Books, Dec. 1912-1914 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Check Books, 1915, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Deeds, Power of Attorney and Certificates of Redemption (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Deeds, Power of Attorney and Abstract of Title (Ellen Nunn) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Ledger of payments to family, 1848-1871 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Ledger-Cash Paid, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Ledger-Expenses, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Letterfile A-H (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Letterfile I-K (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Letterfile L-S (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Letterfile T-Z (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - L.L. Nunn Estate Taxes, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - L.L. Nunn Estate Taxes, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Montezuma Ore Returns (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stubbs & Jakway, [1899] (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Telluride Realty Company, 1908-1915 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company- Joseph Keeler, March 29, 1911-January 15, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company, Jan. 15, 1913-Feb. 14, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company, Jan. March 16, 1915-Dec. 31, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company I, Dec. 28, 1918-July 7, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company II, Dec. 28, 1918-July 7, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Nunn Will and Testament, Family Tree Genealogy (Box 30)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company I, July 31, 1922-Dec. 31, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Utah Lake and Irrigation Company II, July 31, 1922-Dec. 31, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Publications belonging to Nunn
    - "General Ames and His Family" from the Puritan (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Hearst's International Cosmopolitan article about robbery of Nunn's bank and proceeding chase of robbers (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - "Elko County and its Vast Mineral Wealth," by Elko Chamber of Commerce, August 1907 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - News Clippings found in Nunn's Provo office (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Religious Texts (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Photographs
    - L.L. Nunn’s nephews and niece - children of Joseph J. Nunn, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Available online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/30382
    - Portrait of L.L. (print) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - After the "Act" (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - W. J. Carlin photo album made for Nunn (Box 61)
    - Nunn photo album (Box 61)
  - Miscellany and Nunn's Personal Effects
    - Nunn's File on Campbell Suit (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Folder from Nunn's office desk in Provo, Utah found intact at Deep Springs 1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Funeral Notices/Obituaries (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - List of Books, Pamphlets, etc. taken by H.R. Waldo (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - List of contents of box maked "L.L. Nunn, Personal" (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Personal File "G", 1906-1907 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Note Pad (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Note Pads and Memo Books (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Railroad Passes I, 1900-1910 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Railroad Passes II, 1900-1910 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Railroad Passes III, 1900-1910 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Railroad Passes IV, 1900-1910 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Received from Helen Heckman, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Includes description of contents; Negatives, prints, photos, San Miguel Mining Co. stock certificate
    - Reports re: Delta County Property, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Reports re: Delta County Property (copy), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Union Pacific County Map (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - University of Illinois Physicians and Surgeons Faculty and Students, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - University of Michigan Engineering Department Commencement Invitation, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 2 Stiff Collars, MU-769-770 (Box 70)
    - Souvenir photos of Munich (Box 70)
    - Clip holding L.L.'s membership card in Commercial Club, Salt Lake City, and strip of railroad tickets, discounted, MU-773 (Box 70)
      Cards have been removed from the clip and placed in an envelope
    - Collapsible (folding) ruler and metric ruler, MU-765, MU-780 (Box 70)
    - Small glass pot, MU-784 (Box 70)
    - Blue and white forget-me-nots, MU-771 (Box 70)
    - Photo-paperweight, MU-772 (Box 70)
    - Wooden top, MU-764 (Box 70)
    - Box for Waterman fountain-pen, with wooden pen-holder, MU-768 (Box 70)
    - L.L. Nunn embossed wallet containing railroad tickets, MU-766 (Box 70)
    - Broken toy train engine and wagon, MU-778-779 (Box 70)
    - 2 rubber stamps - L.L. Nunn, Telluride Power Co., ink-pad, souvenir box, MU-774-777 (Box 70)
    - 4 engraved calling-cards, L.L. Nunn (Box 70)
    - Box of tiny koh-i-noor pencils, for screwing into drafting tools, MU-789 (Box 70)
    - Key, nail file, and metal clasp on blue ribbon, MU-781, MU-788, MU-793 (Box 70)
    - Piece of Roofing, MU-791 (Box 70)
    - Desk-set with brass name plate, pen from the Hotel Roberts, penholder and pencils, MU-782-783, MU-790, MU-792 (Box 70)
    - 2 twists of black-coated wire, MU-794-795 (Box 70)
    - 2 Lengths of original copper line, Ames to Telluride, MU-786-787 (Box 70)
- Series II. Carroll Whitman
  - Correspondence
    - Armington, Agnes Fuller I, 1910-1911 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Armington, Agnes Fuller II, 1910-1911 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Armington, Agnes Fuller, 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Armington, Agnes Fuller, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bailey, Clyde S. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Engel, Anne, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hughes, Lacy, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Anne I (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Anne II (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Kaufman, Lulubel I (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Kaufman, Lulubel II (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Kaufman, Lulubel III (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Kaufman, Lulubel IV (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - [Kimball] Bernadine, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Meany, Sarah (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous I (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous II (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous III (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Newcombe, D. I (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Newcombe, D. II (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Newcombe, D. III (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Noon, F.C. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Beween L.L. Nunn and Whitman Brothers (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Ruby, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Stafford, Olive (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Wegg, Donald (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Between Whitman Brothers I (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Between Whitman Brothers II (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Between Whitman Brothers III (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Between Whitman Brothers IV (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Between Whitman Family (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Financial Records
    - Cancelled Checks and Bank Book, 1920-1922 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Receipts (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Miscellany
    - Glass Slide "Minute Men, Washington, D.C." (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Hotel Stickers (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Letters and Transcripts, 1875, 1880 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Letters, 1863, 1880, 1882, 1883 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Letters and Transcripts, January-March 1881 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Letters and Transcripts, May-December 1881, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Letters to F. T. Nunn, 1881-1882 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Letters and Transcripts, January-May 1882 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Letters and Transcripts, June-December 1882 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Photocopies of Letters, 1881, 1918, 1938, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Letters to Others, 1906; 1924 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Snippets from Alice Bird's diaries (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Copies of articles (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Copy of poem by Ellen Nunn (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Genealogies (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Linda Nunn Copies (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Cruden's Concordance, Rev. Professor Eadie, 1867 (Box 68)
    - Holy Bible (Box 68)
- Series III. Telluride Power Company and the Power Industry
  - TPC: Correspondence and Related Documents
    - Ashworth, Paul P., [ca. 1915-1956] (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Campbell, J. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Madison Canyon Records (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1902-1911, 1925-1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Noon, F.C. and J.C. Othurs (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Noon, F.C., 1911-1915 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Noon, F.C. and H.E. Smith, 1913-1925 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Nunn, L.L. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Nunn, L.L. - 12 Telegrams, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Nunn, L.L. and Cooper Anderson (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Nunn, P.N., 1899 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Nunn, P.N. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Story, William, 1908, 1927, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Westinghouse, 1894-1904 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wolfrom, C.A. re: Feather River (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Woodhouse, A.L. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Wrench, A.M. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - TPC: Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes
    - Financial Records, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Financial Records, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Financial Records: Employee Compensation Information, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Financial Records: F.D. Olmsted's Tools (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Financial Records & Meeting Minutes: Provo, Utah, 1904-1910 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Financial Records & Related Correspondence: Provo, Utah, 1905-1906 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Financial Records: Audits, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Financial Records & Related Correspondence, 1932-1940 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Financial Records & Related Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Financial Records & Related Correspondence, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes I, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes II, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Financial Records & Meeting Minutes, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Financial Records, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Financial Records, Related Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - TPC: Legal Documents
    - Agreement between Ouray Electric Power & Light Co. and L.L. Nunn, August 1, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Agreement between TPC & The Electric Company, Provo Utah (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Agreement between TPC & Union Pacific Railroad for Wire Crossing (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Proposition for Rock Creek Power and Irrigation (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Testimonial by Adney - "Hidden Tales of Bear River & Related Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Testimony by L.L. Nunn re: Bear Lake (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Trust Deed to Mercantile Trust Company and George N. Chandler (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - TPC: Papers, Address & Reports
    - "Precedent in Electrical Rates," by P.N. Nunn, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - "Electrical Rates - A Study," by P.N. Nunn and Arthury Jobson, October 22, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Early Experiences in the Power Industry, an Address by P.N. Nunn before the American Institute of Electrical Engineers, May 8, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Oval drawing, mounted of Original Power Station Ames Colorado, 1890. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      See also Box 46 Item 72
    - Donnor Pass Undeveloped Water Power Tributary Report (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Feather River Report (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Feather River, Great Western Power Co. Report, March 12, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General Physical Report, Jan. 31, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Historical Report - "Early Telluride History," by A.D. Smith, Sept. 29, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Salmon River Power Development Report (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Skokomish River Water Power Development Report, by Frank Mackean, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stockholders Report, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Various Branches- Reports, Sept. 1903 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Various Branches- Reports and correspondence, 1905-1906 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - TPC: News Clippings, Articles & Other Publications
    - News Clippings & Articles re: TPC and Power Industry I, 1912-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings & Articles re: TPC and Power Industry II, 1912-1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets & Articles, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters & Articles, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters & News Clippings, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Newsletters & News Clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - General Electric Review 9/1956 - "We Did Not Know What Watts Were..., by P.N. Nunn, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Line - "Telluride", 1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Circuit - "Nunn's Plant Olmstead Receive Historic Recognition", Nov. 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cassier's Magazine - "Pioneer Work of the Telluride Power Company," by P.N. Nunn, January 1905 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Available online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/30381
    - Telluride Power, June 2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - TPC: Maps, Drawings, Blueprints, Graphs, Charts, Etc.
    - Beaver River Power Co. - Working Drawings for Air Blast Lightning Arrestor (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Blueprints - Electric Heat Exchanger (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Early Drawings of Apparatus (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Load Factor Effect on Cost (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Lake Hope, Blueprint - Proposed Pipelines (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Load Curves, August 1908 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Madison River Canon - Preliminary Survey, 1905-1909 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Olmstead - Blueprint of Olmstead (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Olmstead - Graph of Span-Sag Curves of Copper Cable, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Olmstead - Map of Grounds, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Oneida Narrows - Map (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Oneida Reservoir - County Map (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Provo, Utah - Chart of Rating Curve, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Territory Served by TPC - Map (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Topographic Maps (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Utah Dept. - Recapitulation of Market, 1905-1909 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - TPC: Photographs, Illustrations, & Negatives
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Feather River (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - [Oneida Narrows] Blueprint Photographs (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Salmon & Beaver Rivers - Negatives, Summer 1969 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - TPC: Miscellany
    - Annual Picnic Announcements, Golden Anniversary, 1932-1941 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Annual Picnic Announcements, 1947-1948, 1951-1952, & 1954 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Biography - Paul P. Ashworth (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Corporate History (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Electric Light War, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - TPC Envelopes (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Illium Plant Postcard (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Record Book - [Water Levels], 1903-1904 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Specifications, 1903, 1906, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 53)